sharefile.com 2007-12-26

# ShareFile - Privacy Policy

ShareFile is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the ShareFile domain (www.sharefile.com). Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

Additionally, ShareFile is committed to adhering to the privacy principles of the Safe Harbor Program administered by the U.S. Dept. of Commerce (<http://export.gov/safeharbor>). 

This privacy policy was last updated on 9/27/2007. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our support team at 1-800-441-3453 or support@sharefile.com. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed within 30 days, you should contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

At ShareFile, we respect and protect the privacy of our customers and those who use our websites. The following Privacy Statement provides details about how your personal information is collected and used. This privacy statement applies to the products and services that are located on the www.sharefile.com domain. 

## Information Collection and Use

ShareFile is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. ShareFile collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

In order to use ShareFile, companies must complete a registration process either on our web site or via telephone or email. During registration, you must provide contact information (such as name and email address) for at least one person at your company. We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. Often, credit card information is also required during registration. If you do not want to provide your credit card information, ShareFile allows you to sign up for a free trial by calling us at 1-800-441-3453 or sending an email request to support@sharefile.com. ShareFile also has an invoice billing option for companies that are not able to provide credit card information. 

ShareFile reserves the right to contact users who sign up for a free trial, or begin the signup process for a free trial, to assist with the registration process and/or gain feedback about the system. If you wish to unsubscribe from receiving promotional emails during the free trial period, please use the unsubscribe link in the email itself or email us at support@sharefile.com. 

Once a company creates an account with ShareFile, that company can optionally create accounts for employees and clients. In order to create an account for employees, the email address of the employee as well as the first and last name of the employee must be provided. You may optionally provide the employee's company name and/or time zone. We may add the email address of employees to our company email newsletter. When adding clients to the system, companies must at minimum provide an email address for the client, which is used as a login to securely access data on ShareFile. The client may also be required to enter their first name and last name and can optionally provide their company name and time zone information. We will never add the email addresses of client users to our email newsletter. 

Emails from the ShareFile Support Team may be sent in the case of important notifications. These emails will be sent only to registered employees (not clients). 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters or promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by emailing us at support@sharefile.com, or you may contact us at 1-800-441-3453 or at 510 Glenwood Avenue, Suite 221, Raleigh, NC 27603 to opt-out. 

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may correct or update it by making the change in the "My Settings" portion of our system or by contacting customer support at support@sharefile.com or 1-800-441-3453 or at 510 Glenwood Avenue, Suite 221, Raleigh, NC 27603. If you would like to have all of your files and personal information completely removed from our system, please contact us using any of the above methods. 

## Sharing and Usage

We will never share, sell, or rent your personal information with third parties for their promotional use. Occasionally, we enter into contracts with third parties so that they can assist us in servicing you. 

For example, ShareFile uses a third-party (Cybersource) to process credit card transactions. This company is forbidden from using your personal information for any other purpose than billing your account. Additionally, ShareFile uses third-party software for web analytics to help understand the usage patterns on our web site. No personally identifiable information is included in ShareFile's web analytics. 

Our third-party contracts prohibit these vendors from using any of your personal information for their own purposes, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information we provide to them. We may disclose or report personal information in limited circumstances where we believe in good faith that disclosure is required under the law. For example, we may be required to disclose personal information to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities, to comply with a legal process such as court order, subpoena, search warrant, or law enforcement request. 

## Use of Web Technologies

We use a variety of technologies on our sites. Among these are cookies; a piece of information that our websites provide to your browser when you visit our sites. Cookies allow us to verify the login status of customers using products or services linked directly with our website, track point of entry to point of registration for those users participating in our affiliate signup programs, and to track and measure the success of a particular marketing campaign. Cookies also allow us to track overall site usage and determine areas users prefer, enabling us to make your visit to our websites easier by recognizing you when you return and helping to provide you with a customized experience. If you choose to disable cookies, you may still use our site; however, you may have limited access to some areas within our websites. Session cookies are cookies which are automatically deleted once you close your web browser. Session cookies are required in order to use the ShareFile application. 

We do not store any personally identifiable information in cookies (except for your email address if you elect for the site to remember your login information), however, we may use unique identifiers in cookies to help us map your usage to your User ID, which in turn ties to data in our internal databases which may include personally identifiable information. We also keep track of activity on our website via log files stored on our web servers. We collect information such as IP address, browser type and version, and pages you view. We also keep track of how you got to our site and any links you click on to leave our site. Once you leave our site, we do not track you. We use your website activity to assist us in offering you a personalized Web experience, assist you with technical support, diagnose problems with our server, administer our websites and to tailor our product and service offerings to you. 

If you use our web site and then subsequently sign up for ShareFile, we may associate your web site logs with personally identifiable information about you such as your name and contact information. This information is kept on our internal databases only and is not shared with third parties. It is used to help us better understand which parts of our web site are most effective for users. 

If you use the ShareFile application, we track your upload and download history as well as certain other pages you visit in our system log. This log is used for support purposes to help troubleshoot problems that you may have with the system and parts of the log may also be viewable by administrators, employees, and/or clients in your account for audit tracking purposes. 

## Testimonials

We post testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as a customer's name and company name. We obtain a customer's permission before posting testimonials to our web site, and customers may request that their testimonial be removed from our web site by contacting support@sharefile.com or calling 1-800-441-3453. Requests for removal from our web site will be fulfilled within 7 business days. 

## Links

Some of our sites provide links to third-party websites, such as those of our business partners and online advertisers. While on these sites, ShareFile or its partners may collect information about you. Because ShareFile does not control the information policies or practices of these third parties, you should review their privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use personally identifiable information. 

## Security

We take every precaution to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information by using industry-recognized security safeguards such as firewalls, coupled with carefully developed security procedures to protect your information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration. When we ask for sensitive information, such as credit card numbers, we protect it through the use of encryption during transmission, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

ShareFile takes care to reinforce the importance of our website visitors' security and privacy among our employees. Our employees are trained and required to safeguard your information and, using physical, electronic and procedural safeguards, we restrict access to personal information to those employees and agents for business purposes only. Additionally, we use internal and external resources to review the adequacy of our security procedures. 

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, link to it from our home page (www.sharefle.com), and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
